<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Visual Azure</title>
    <link>https://sketchnote.dev/visual-azure/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Visual Azure</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sketchnote.dev/visual-azure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Learn Together!</title>
      <link>https://sketchnote.dev/visual-azure/posts/hello-visual-learner/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sketchnote.dev/visual-azure/posts/hello-visual-learner/</guid>
      <description>Yes, it’s 2021. We’re already a month into the New Year! And if you are like me and many others, you’ve probably made a resolution to learn something new, or skill up on something you already have experience with.
  A Visual Guide To Azure
  My 2021 resolution:
Learn all things Azure by completing all Fundamentals learning paths and validating my knowledge with relevant certfications! Specifically, these three &amp;ndash; in this order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join The Community!</title>
      <link>https://sketchnote.dev/visual-azure/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 12:28:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sketchnote.dev/visual-azure/community/</guid>
      <description>Having a study group or learning community can help you progress in your learning goals in two ways. First, by giving you a sense of accountability that ensures you keep making progress. Second, by creating a sense of belonging (in a shared journey toward certifications) that can lead to new insights and friendships.
I&amp;rsquo;m exploring GitHub Discussion Forums to support community interactions around this project. Want to join the conversations? Please do start by introducing yourself and share your learning objectives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Guide</title>
      <link>https://sketchnote.dev/visual-azure/guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 18:44:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sketchnote.dev/visual-azure/guide/</guid>
      <description>Learning Roadmap We&amp;rsquo;ll start with these Beginner-Friendly Certifications for Azure.
 AZ-900: Azure Fundamentals DP-900: Azure Data Fundamentals AI-900: Azure AI Fundamentals  Each certification lists the recommended learning paths for preparation (see below).
Azure Fundamentals: AZ-900 We&amp;rsquo;ll start with the foundational course to learn cloud computing concepts (general) and cloud computing services and solutions (specific to Azure). The roadmap below is color-coded to highlight the key paths, and the single shared module (Intro to Azure Fundamentals) that anchors them all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About #VisualAzure</title>
      <link>https://sketchnote.dev/visual-azure/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sketchnote.dev/visual-azure/about/</guid>
      <description>VisualAzure is a visual storytelling project with three objectives:
 Consistency | Build a visual vocabulary for Azure &amp;ndash; starting with Azure Fundamentals . Content | Create a visual study guide for Azure Certifications - starting with AZ-900. Community | Support learning conversations using the related Discussions forum.  What is a visual vocabulary? | A visual vocabulary uses graphical elements (images, iconography, typography, composition) to communicate ideas or concepts to an audience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
